(Penny:)...I dreamed of moving to L.A.
and becoming a movie star.
(Penny:)Anyway, after four years
of acting lessons and waiting tables...
...I've done a hemorrhoid
commercial...
(Penny:)...and a production of Anne Frank
above a bowling alley.
(Penny:)So you know, dreams do come true.
(Penny:)- Your turn.
- Uh, let's see. Ahem. Uh...
(Leonard:)I am an experimental physicist
at CaItech.
(Leonard:)Most of my research
is with high-powered lasers, and...
Oh, l've just gotten
a big government grant...
(Leonard:)...to see if they can be used
to knock out incoming ballistic missiles.
- Wow. Can they?
- Oh, God, no.
But the money's pretty good.
(Leonard:)And I used the equipment
to make my own Bat-Signal.
(Penny:)Bat-Signal?
What are you, some kind of nerd?
(Leonard:)Not some kind of nerd,
I am the king of nerds.